The thing you hear is drawing down In
this quiet, sleepy little town
The late night talks, the secret shed The only
one who ever dared To see the world the way I do To
know my heart is safe with you No need for words,
no need to guess Just a quiet, perfect happiness
Cause you're my anchor in the storm You keep me
safe, you keep me warm More than a friend, a
different heart The other half of my own heart
This isn't some cheap romance phase Through all
my nights and all my days You're the truest thing
I'll ever know And I will never let you go
The world outside might not understand
The simple comfort of your hand
The quiet trust when you would stay And chase the
shadows all away No walls between us, nothing
hid Just two lost and lonely kids Who found a
board in a raging sea You found a sanctuary in me
Cause you're my anchor in the storm You keep me
safe, you keep me warm More than a friend, a
different art The other half of my own heart This
isn't some cheap romance phase Through all my
nights and all my days You're the truest thing
I'll ever know And I will never let you go
Bye.
Aum
Aum Aum